I prepared the insurance claim documents.
Good job.
Yes, sir.
INSURANCE CLAIM FORM
Around the world,
ugly deals happen behind closed doors.
Just a moment, sir.
A single medical certificate.
A one-line accident report.
As you trace the hidden truth
on that sheet of paper,
you may come across scumbags
who trade human lives for money.
Digging into all of this…
is my job.
It's gone cold.
Add more steam.
Damn it.
Hey.
Who the hell are you?
Relax.
I'm not in your line of work.
You're out of your damn mind.
Do you know who I am?
I noticed you were pretty well insured.
How many should I chop off?
Kim, a man in his thirties,
has been arrested for arranging
intentional finger amputations
to claim workers' compensation payouts
worth billions of won.
Kim used promises of high profit
to recruit participants,
persuaded them to amputate their fingers,
and had them sign up for workers' comp,
ultimately pocketing around
three billion won in fraudulent claims.
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
The police have uncovered a scheme
in which job seekers,
including foreign workers,
were lured into work
and intentionally harmed on the job
to collect tens of billions of won
in insurance…
Thanks to you, Mr. Cha,
we lost another group contract.
Right.
But we saved over ten times on the payout.
Yes.
Excuse me?
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
It's not just any barber shop,
but a private one.
Right, and it's members-only.
Of course, we'll make sure
you're compensated.
Yes, I'm sorry about that.
What's the point of saving on the payout
if all the operating funds
go to cleaning up after you?
Maybe I'll take a vacation, then.
With no operating funds,
I might as well rest.
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm just asking you not to overdo it.
You could call the police
instead of handling it yourself.
You know they never arrive on time.
Mr. Cha! I've got bad news.
Do you remember Chae-rin?
This is all my fault.
I've been struggling to get by
since my divorce
and had to leave my child alone.
I know you're worried,
but I heard what happened from her.
It's a huge relief
that you have insurance.
My poor Chae-rin.
I don't know what to do now.
She has third-degree burns
on 40% of her body.
Her mother already filed
an insurance claim.
I rubbed my eyes a lot
while I was asleep…
and couldn't see the next day.
1 YEAR AGO
Really?
Yes.
But my mom gave me a lot of pocket money
because I had a rough time being unwell.
With this, you can play video games,
buy snacks,
and even try the claw machine.
Are you giving this to me?
Yes.
Thank you.
Mr. Cha.
It really was an accident.
I was trying to eat instant noodles,
but I spilled them.
Chae-rin…
I'll stop by tomorrow for a test drive.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Big money coming in, I see.
Fifty million won for loss of vision.
Seventy million for the burn injuries.
What's next?
The police ruled it an accident.
Who are you to say anything?
You still call yourself a mother?
That kid is lying
to protect a mother like you…
even though she almost died.
I'll make sure…
to put you behind bars.
VIP INVITATION SPECIAL AUCTION
This way.
I'm looking forward to this.
What's this?
Ms. Kim, you must've worked so hard.
Not at all.
When did you prepare this?
Just look at the colors.
Now this is art.
Well done!
It's all thanks to you.
Hey!
-What the heck?
-Are you insane?
Do you know how much this is worth?
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
That's what I want to ask.
Ms. Han!
Tell me what the hell is going on!
Please get rid of this
before the clients arrive.
How could you tear up a work of art?
You're the chief auctioneer.
Which is it?
If you knew it was a forgery,
then you committed a crime.
If you didn't,
then you don't deserve
to be an auctioneer.
It's not a forgery.
It was consigned to me
by Artist Jeong's son.
Artist Jeong
suffered a stroke
and is in a nursing facility.
He can't even hold a brush.
But the appraiser said…
Had we sold that painting,
not only would it have humiliated
the auction house,
but it would've made you legally liable.
I'm going to investigate this thoroughly,
so be prepared.
THE LATE CHA WOO-HEE
OCTOBER 8, 1993 - AUGUST 28, 2020
Although the circumstances are suspicious,
there's no objective evidence
that the accident was intentional.
You bastard.
Let go of me!
Keep still!
REDEVELOPMENT THAT IGNORES
THE RESIDENTS MUST STOP!
HYUN-SU'S FRUIT
I didn't lie like my friends did
and was honest about
taking a trip with my boyfriend.
So trust me, okay?
POLICYHOLDER: CHA WOO-HEE
BENEFICIARY: JU HYUN-SU
As only the charge of causing
the victim's death through negligence
has been sustained,
the defendant, Ju Hyun-su,
is hereby sentenced to one year in prison.
I'll never be fooled again.
Never.
MAY YOU ALWAYS ACHIEVE GREATER SUCCESS
VIP INVITATION SPECIAL AUCTION
Ms. Han is here.
We'll begin now.
This is Black Ink & Light
by Ahn Byeong-woon.
We'll open at 100 million won
and take bids
in ten million won increments.
100 million?
110 million?
120 million?
130 million?
Next up, we have Genuine Comfort
by Hanna Lien.
This is a symbolic piece
that embodies pets as a metaphor
to reflect the essence of human society.
I look forward to seeing
who the successful bidder will be.
160 million won? At 160 million.
170 million won?
Now, for the moment
we've been waiting for.
The highlight of today's auction,
Universe by Choi Jung-soo.
This is a monumental work by Choi Jung-soo
that pushes the boundaries
of contemporary painting.
This piece combines painting, textiles,
and the physical properties of light,
making it one of their signature works.
This lot is expected to achieve
the highest bid of today's auction.
Let's open the bidding.
4.85 billion won?
We have 4.85 billion.
4.9 billion won?
We have a 4.9 billion absentee bid.
4.95 billion won?
We have 4.95 billion won.
Five billion won?
We have a five billion won absentee bid.
5.05 billion?
We have 5.05 billion won.
The highest bid so far
is 5.05 billion won.
5.1 billion?
I'm checking the floor.
We have 5.1 billion.
We received a bid for 5.1 billion.
5.15 billion?
We have 5.15 billion.
5.2 billion won?
We have 5.2 billion.
Paddle 86 currently holds
the highest bid at 5.2 billion won.
Anyone at 5.25 billion?
We have 5.25 billion for Paddle 64.
Looking for 5.3 billion.
Yes, Paddle 86.
We have 5.3 billion.
That's the highest bid.
Let me ask bidders in the room
and on the phone again.
5.35 billion?
It may take a little while to decide,
so I'll give you some time to consider.
We're bidding at 5.35 billion won.
I'll call it three times
before closing the bidding.
5.35 billion?
After an intense bidding,
Paddle 86 has secured the lot
at 5.3 billion won.
Come on.
I give up.
What if Mr. Song sees you?
Why are you still here?
For market research.
I want to see which type of champagne
the guests prefer.
Seriously? You didn't say a word earlier.
You're already dealing with a lot,
so I didn't want to bother you.
I'll leave after a bit.
By the way,
she's the associate auctioneer, right?
Why do you ask?
No reason.
I just get a bad vibe from her.
I'll be back.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Thank you for helping me
secure such a great piece today.
I've only placed bids online before,
but live auctions are much more fun.
I noticed you eyeing that piece
at the auction preview,
so I knew you'd be here today.
You remember me?
I don't believe we've actually met before.
Once I see someone, I don't forget them.
You don't forget, huh?
Ever?
I'm Paek Jun-beom.
I'm Han Seol-ah.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
You're Mr. Paek Jun-beom,
CEO of Your Home, right?
The artwork you selected today
was exceptional.
I hear you've got all
the most sought-after pieces these days.
This is our associate auctioneer.
She's very good at what she does,
so I'll leave you two to talk.
Please excuse me.
Wait…
I'm Kim Yun-ji.
If you have any pieces to consign
for the next auction,
please allow me to handle them.
"Associate Auctioneer Kim Yun-ji"?
Yes, sir.
You don't know when to step in
and when to stay back, do you?
TRANQUILIZER
Ms. Kim, we're still on the job.
So?
I smell alcohol on you.
You should be careful
when you deal with VIPs.
Are you sure you're not just upset
that I butted in earlier?
Ms. Kim Yun-ji.
Let's behave like professionals.
You know,
you've got quite the mental strength.
You're definitely a professional, Ms. Han.
Isn't wanting to die
the normal response at this point?
What are you trying to say?
I'm curious.
If the secret you've been hiding
is out in the open,
would you still be so composed?
I'm curious to see the look on your face
when I take the main podium from you.
The main podium?
With your skills?
I won't hold back anymore.
Enjoy what time you have left.
Not that there's much of it.
Hello?
Mr. Cha Woo-seok?
Yes. Who's this?
I want to report insurance fraud.
Insurance fraud?
Sure, go ahead.
It's a murder.
A murder committed
for an insurance payout.
Why did you call me instead of the police?
The police can't be trusted.
They dismissed this case as an accident.
I've heard rumors about you.
Once you're after something,
you never let it go.
You're the only person I can trust now.
I'll tell you everything I know.
When did you get here?
Just let me sleep.
I've been on a stakeout
for three days in a row.
Go home and sleep comfortably, then.
It's too far.
Where are you going at this hour?
I got a tip
about a murder-for-insurance case.
Go back to being a cop already.
It's in your jurisdiction.
Your call cannot be connected.
You will be directed to voicemail,
and charges will apply after the…
She's not answering.
What the heck?
SIU INVESTIGATOR CHA WOO-SEOK
MISSED CALL
Please don't take any photos!
Move out of the way!
Three meters?
Yes, they said she landed
three meters away from the exterior wall.
The distance doesn't quite add up.
No, it doesn't.
If she'd slipped or committed suicide,
she would've landed within two meters.
Secure the CCTV footage
from the auction house,
and trace her whereabouts
around the time of the fall.
Got it.
Her legs, lower back, ribs, and spine
have all been fractured.
The fracture pattern is typical of a fall.
The direct cause of death is organ failure
due to multiple fractures.
Is this a suicide, then?
That's the most plausible hypothesis,
but I found minute petechiae
around her neck and inside her lips.
Are you saying she was strangled?
No.
The petechiae are too faint
to make that conclusion.
But it's possible
someone suddenly grabbed her by the neck.
GANGHA POLICE STATION
This can't be a coincidence.
What happened?
The victim was going to report
an insurance-related murder.
So you went to see her,
and she just fell to her death?
Yes, sir.
And Cha Woo-seok received the tip?
Hey, Ggong.
You and I will handle this case.
Excuse me?
Sir, Eun-gyeom and I can…
I won't have Cha Woo-seok
poking around in our jurisdiction.
But you're okay with running into him?
He won't be okay with it,
since he still thinks
I let his sister's killer walk free.
Is that what you think too?
I think we all did what we could
from our own point of view.
A case has no point of view.
There's only the truth.
And if you can't accept that,
you'll end up like Cha Woo-seok.
We'll investigate again
since you filed a report,
but if she continues to deny it,
there's nothing else we can do.
Goodbye, then.
What should we do?
We'll come every day
to show her there are other adults
who will protect her.
You head back first.
I'm going to stop by Royal Auction.
Okay.
Oh, Ms. Kim Yun-ji's case
was ruled a suicide, right?
This month marks two years
since she took out the policy,
and the suicide exclusion period
has passed too.
She wanted to report a murder
committed for an insurance payout.
An hour before she died.
Would someone
on the verge of suicide do that?
-Let me give you a hand.
-Oh, thank you.
Damn it.
That's it!
The blades turned away.
Funny how it worked when you showed up.
I guess Ms. Kim didn't like you.
Our company is a mess right now.
My apologies.
Chair Kim.
The police are coming to investigate.
This final year of misfortune
is making quite a commotion.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I should've been more attentive
to my team member.
I'll take care of the police.
Well, you're in charge of PR as well,
so you should.
Then what's the point
of having a managing director?
Right, it makes more sense that I meet
with them on behalf of the company.
They'll want to speak with someone
who worked closely with Ms. Kim.
If Mr. Song talks to them,
it could make the situation
seem more serious.
You sure you'll be okay?
Yes.
I'll make sure this is dealt with quietly.
All right.
Quietly…
I like the sound of that.
Hello.
I'm Chief Auctioneer Han Seol-ah
at Royal Auction.
I'm Detective Pyo Seong-il
from Gangha Police Station.
I'm Gong Joo-young.
This is just a basic inquiry
into the incident,
so there's no need to feel any pressure.
Okay, please take a seat.
Okay.
First off,
can you tell me about that night?
There was an event exclusive
to Royal Auction VIP members,
followed by an after-party
that went on until around 10 p.m.
What role did Ms. Kim Yun-ji have?
She was an associate auctioneer.
No CCTV cameras
in the emergency staircase.
A murder committed
for an insurance payout.
I'll tell you everything I know.
After that, she committed suicide here?
Did you notice anything unusual
about Ms. Kim that day?
Did she perhaps get into an argument
with someone?
She seemed fine from what I could tell.
As her colleague, do you have any idea
what might've happened?
I didn't know much about her private life.
CHIEF AUCTIONEER: HAN SEOL-AH
How many auctioneers
does the company have?
Ms. Kim and I are the only ones
who actually run the auctions.
Everyone else is still in training.
Can we get the list of event participants?
The VIP list is confidential,
so it can't be released.
They're witnesses who were at the scene.
One of them could be a suspect.
Is there any evidence
that it was a murder?
Your colleague is dead,
but protecting your clients
is more important to you?
Detective Gong.
Please bring a warrant.
If you have more questions,
please send them in writing.
When was the last time
you saw Ms. Kim Yun-ji that day?
Where were you
at the time of the incident?
Was that a difficult question?
It seems like you can't answer.
I was in the Auction Team office.
I didn't see her again
after the after-party.
This is the extent of the cooperation
I can provide.
If it seems too perfect,
there's a good chance it's not true.
I'll look into Han Seol-ah
and her relationship with Kim Yun-ji.
So there is something, huh?
I don't expect much from the police,
but let's help each other out.
No thanks.
Forget the easy way
and go the long way, then.
Just go sell insurance.
You still think you're a detective?
I get that a lot from my boss.
Let's go.
It's funny how cops
are good at taking small bribes,
but they can't sniff out big money.
Watch yourself.
Why are you angry?
Do you have regrets?
Do I make you uncomfortable?
You little bastard.
What are you two doing?
You can't do this here!
Hey, Ggong.
If even one investigation detail
gets leaked to the insurance company,
be prepared to lose your job.
TYPE: PERFECT ONLIFE SWITCH INSURANCE
POLICYHOLDER: KIM YUN-JI
Kim Yun-ji was treated for depression
for a long time.
I'm seeing a lot of signs
that point to suicide.
What did the people
at the auction house say?
The chief auctioneer showed up,
but she wasn't cooperative.
Han Seol-ah, was it?
It's this woman.
ART AUCTION HOUSE "ROYAL AUCTION"
REVENUE UP 28% FROM LAST YEAR
Han Seol-ah.
HAN SEOL-AH
FIRST FEMALE CHIEF AUCTIONEER
AT ROYAL AUCTION
THE CINDERELLA OF THE AUCTION WORLD
CHIEF AUCTIONEER HAN SEOL-AH
"I DON'T LOOK, I READ THE ROOM"
"PEOPLE THINK AUCTIONEERS JUST CALL BIDS…"
HAN SEOL-AH ENTERED THE AUCTION WORLD
8 YEARS AGO…
"WINNING A BID
COMES DOWN TO TRUST AND TIMING"
AUCTIONEER
Please stop crying.
Yun-ji…
I feel so sorry for her.
She was excited about debuting soon.
Debut?
Mr. Song promised to get rid of Ms. Han
and promote Yun-ji in her place.
Really?
Why?
That's not what's important right now!
Look at what happened to Yun-ji!
It's Ms. Han.
It's probably a battery problem.
Your smart key, I mean.
I guess you're right.
Don't call a tow truck.
I'll help you.
Your key fob, please.
Hold the key fob against the start button
and press it.
It should start your car.
Thank you. I owe you one.
You can pay me back.
If we ever meet again, that is.
SOCHEON FUNERAL SERVICE
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
VIEW INSURANCE POLICY
KIM YUN-JI
TYPE: PERFECT ONLIFE SWITCH INSURANCE
PARTIES TO THE POLICY
POLICYHOLDER: KIM YUN-JI
AUTO PAYMENT ACCOUNT DETAILS
NAME: JANGWON BANK
HAN SEOL-AH
What?
POLICYHOLDER: YOON SEUNG-JAE
Yoon Seung-jae.
Thirty-five years old.
The total death benefit
is 700 million won.
The beneficiary is…
BENEFICIARY: HAN SEOL-AH
Han Seol-ah?
POLICY CHANGE HISTORY
Canceled?
YOON SEUNG-JAE
PHONE NUMBER: 010-0532-9655
The phone you are trying to reach
is turned off.
You will be directed to voicemail
after the beep and charges…
Hello?
Is this Mr. Yoon Seung-jae's home?
Yes. Who's this?
Hello, I'm Cha Woo-seok,
an SIU investigator.
I need to confirm
a few insurance-related matters.
May I speak to Mr. Yoon Seung-jae?
Seung-jae…
is dead.
He died ten days ago.
CHANGE DETAILS: CANCELLATION (WITHDRAWAL)
DATE: MAY 23, 2025
The bride needs to smile more.
Are you nervous?
You look so stiff.
Give me a big smile.
Now face each other.
Nice.
That's nice.
See? It's much better
now that you're smiling.
POLICYHOLDER: YOON SEUNG-JAE
He paid the 200 million premium upfront.
It's a VIP-only insurance policy
for high-net-worth individuals.
I think this is the case
Kim Yun-ji was going to report.
I'm going to the police station.
Hey, hold on.
GUARANTEE INSURANCE
WITHDRAWAL/CANCELLATION CONFIRMATION
What's this?
It's a cancellation.
Oh, you're right.
This won't even count toward performance,
so why…
Where did he go?
Is he in detective mode again?
I never should've brought him here, right?
It's all my fault, right?
Her fiancé died just ten days ago.
Did she file an insurance claim?
No, that's the strange part.
The policy was canceled
right before he died.
Why did he do that?
Kim Yun-ji definitely knew something.
Han Seol-ah
was about to lose
her chief auctioneer title to Kim Yun-ji.
From where Han Seol-ah stands,
Kim Yun-ji's death ended all her troubles.
Look into the details
of her fiancé's death.
Okay.
Han Seol-ah's fiancé
was in a yacht accident.
AUTOPSY RESULTS RULE THE DEATH AS DROWNING
Drowning?
We meet again.
Let me officially introduce myself.
I'm Cha Woo-seok, an SIU investigator.
NONGHYUP LIFE INSURANCE
SIU SENIOR MANAGER CHA WOO-SEOK
Ms. Kim Yun-ji was a client of ours.
That's why I'm investigating
whether her death was a suicide
or…
a murder.
You sound like a detective.
Do SIU investigators
handle actual investigations too?
We at least look into it.
I told the police everything I know.
You didn't mention she was competing
for the chief auctioneer position.
I never considered her as my competition.
How do you feel?
Tens of billions of won
are in your hands to decide.
Raising a couple of hundred million won
would be a piece of cake.
I bet money doesn't even feel real to you.
I wonder what your salary is.
I get the feeling that a regular salary
wouldn't satisfy you.
An auctioneer is no different
from a regular office worker.
It must be hard
for a regular office worker like you
to be constantly compared
to wealthy clients
and to need nice clothes
and a nice car for the job.
That's what most people think,
only judging by what they see.
If you're done talking, please excuse me.
Yoon Seung-jae.
This is Gong Joo-young
from Violent Crimes Unit 1.
Hello? I'm listening.
The woman who died at Royal Auction
didn't commit suicide.
She was murdered.
RECORDING
Are you a witness?
Hello?
Yoon Seung-jae.
A successful businessman
who ran a restaurant.
Ten days ago,
he took a yacht out on the river and died.
The death benefit
amounted to 700 million won,
and you were the beneficiary.
You two
weren't family.
He was my fiancé.
Did you already know?
That he canceled his policy
before he died?
Yes.
What a shame.
If he hadn't canceled it,
you could've held 700 million won
in your hands.
You must have a lot of time on your hands
to investigate a canceled policy.
You couldn't receive the death benefit,
but the 200 million won premium
was returned to Mr. Yoon's account.
And you're assuming
that money came my way?
You think I killed my fiancé
for a measly 200 million won?
Tell me.
What does his accident
have to do with what happened to Ms. Kim?
I can smell it.
The stench of someone…
trading human lives for money.
SPECIAL THANKS TO LEE ELIJAH
AND HA SEOKJIN FOR THEIR APPEARANCE
What was Kim Yun-ji trying to reveal
before she was murdered?
You've heard of Yoon Seung-jae, right?
Kim Yun-ji and Yoon Seung-jae met,
and they both died.
Wrongful death?
What about wrongful suspicion?
A love triangle?
The most common motive for murder
is love affairs.
What is it that you really want to know?
Your fiancé and Kim Yun-ji.
Did you kill them?
Subtitle: Jenny Kim